コードギアス反逆のルルーシュR2 TURN 25（最終話）Re；
TURN 25（最終話）Re；
ルルーシュとナナリー
あっ
くっ　うっ
スザクとカレン
逃げ出す人々
カレンとスザクは戦闘中
コーネリアの病室そばにはギルフォード
C.C.
スザクとカレン
ダモクレスの鍵を渡そうとし抵抗するナナリー
ジェレミアとアーニャ
はっ
それを確認しておちていくカレン
ナナリーとルルーシュ
黒の騎士団とC.C.
えっ
そのとき空に爆音が
あっ
とシンクー
2ヶ月後皇帝直轄領?日本
ナナリーの姿も
見守る群衆の声
ロイドさんたちも別の場所で拘束？
こちらへちかづいてくるゼロ
ふっと笑うルルーシュ
回想
顔をゆがませるナナリーとカレン
スザクの回想
涙をながすC.C.
というルルーシュの言葉
あぁ
ナナリーのもとへ
みつめるナナリー
あっ
はっ
おう！
と飛び出すギルフォードと
ナナリーの絶叫
カレンの部屋
ベッドの下には鉄アレイ
コルクボードには学校での楽しい写真
ルルーシュの写真も
学校へいく準備をするカレン
母と暮らしているようです
8年ぶりにお兄さまの顔をみました
For the first time in 8 years,
I've seen your face, big brother.
それが人殺しの顔なのですね
And it's the face of
a murderer, isn't it?
おそらく私も　同じ顔をしているのでしょうね
I probably have
the same face, don't I?
では　やはり今までのフレイヤもおまえが
Then... It's been you firing
the F.L.E.I.J.A.s up till now.
はい　とめるつもりでした
Yes. I wanted to stop this.
To stop you.
お兄様
たとえお兄様が死ぬことになったとしても
Even if that meant
killing you, big brother.
ですからお兄様にフレイヤを
That's why I can't let you have F.L.E.I.J.A....
Why I can't hand over the Damocles key to you.
このダモクレスの鍵をお渡しすることはできません
Even... Even if you use
your Geass on me!
おお兄様が　ギアスをつかわれたとしても！
ナナリーにギアスを使う？
Use Geass on Nunnally?
そうだ俺は何度も望んだはずだろう
It's true. Time after time,
I've wanted to use it on her.
せめてナナリーの目だけでもみえるようにしてやりたいと
At the very least, I wanted
to use it to cure her blindness.
しかし　王の力　絶対遵守のギアスも肝心のナナリーにだけはかけられなかった
The power of the king...
I could never use Geass's
power of absolute submission on Nunnally,
the person
I was doing all of this for.
でも　今ならいやダメだ
But, now... No, I can't!
ナナリーの意志までねじまげたら俺は
If I resort to twisting
even Nunnally's will, then I'm!
Sekai no owari de
At the end of the world
Umareta hikari
The light that's born
Ima kaze no naka
Now blows in the wind
Kireigoto dake jaa ikirenai
Pretty words alone won't sustain you
Yasashisa dake jaa iyasenai
Kindness alone won't heal you
Ubawareta nowa nanda
What is it that was stolen from you
Kawaranai sekai de
In this unchanging world
Kikoetekita nowa nanda
What is it that you hear
Shikisai no uta
A song of color
Everything is bright...
Kudakechitta yume wo
Let our crumbled dreams resound
Asu no hate ni hibikaseru you ni
At the edge of tomorrow
Sekai no owari de
At the end of the world
Umareta hikari
The light that's born
Bokura hitotsu ni
Becomes one with us
Ima kaze no naka
Now blows in the wind
ジノの機体はうごかず
カレン　どうしても邪魔をする気か
Kallen...
You're determined to defy me?
スザク　私はあなたを誤解していた
Suzaku... I misjudged you.
ん？
やり方は違うけれど
Our methods may have differed,
あなたはあなたなりに日本のことを考えていると思っていたの
but I thought you cared about
Japan in your own way. But now!
でも
自分は　俺とルルーシュには
There's something I...
That Lelouch and I have to do.
やらねばならないことがある
そう　そんなに力がほしいの？
I see... You really crave power
that much? In that case...
だったら
In that case, what?
あなたはここにいちゃいけない
In that case, you can't be allowed to live.
I'll defeat you and stop Lelouch!
あなたを倒し　ルルーシュを止める
それは　させない！
I won't let you do that!
再び戦闘
リヴァルは逃げなくてよかったの？
Any second thoughts about
not running away, Rivalz?
どこへ逃げればいいんですか？
Where exactly should I run?
そりゃそうだ
You have a point.
俺はね　みんなと毎日楽しくやっていければ
All I ever wanted was to spend
every day having fun with you all.
それでよかったんですけど
うん　わかるよ
Yeah, I know what you mean.
ジェレミアとアーニャ
主なき力など！
You, power without a master!
何かにたよる弱い男
You need something to depend on.
Such a weak man!
怪我した体でいこうとする藤堂さんをとめる千葉
やめてください！その傷では！
Stop, please!
You're too badly wounded!
始めた責任は　取らねばならぬ
I have to take responsibility
for starting this!
人々を率いる資格とは
That's what gives me
the right to lead others!
ナナリーとルルーシュ
お兄様に
Big brother, you have no right
to take control of the world.
この世界を手にする資格はありません
ゼロを名乗って
Not you, who took the name Zero
and bent peoples' will to your own!
人の心を踏みにじってきたお兄様には
では　あのまま隠れ続ける生活を送ればよかったのか？
Are you saying it would have been better
to continue living our lives in hiding?
暗殺におびえつづける未来が望みだったのか？
Did you want a future of constant fear of
assassination? This was for your future, too.
おまえの未来のためにも
いつ　私がそんなことを頼みましたか
When did I ever
ask you to do this?!
私は　お兄様と二人だけで暮らせれば
I would have been satisfied
just to have been able to live with you!
それだけでよかったのに
しかし　現実は様々なものによって支配されている
But the reality is that we're
controlled by all sorts of things!
抗うことは必要だ
They must be opposed!
カレンとスザク
そのために
That's the reason
I've fought with the resistance!
レジスタンスとして戦ってきたのよ！
組織をつかうという手だってあったはずだ！
You could have tried
to work within the system!
その組織に
And what about the people
who can't get into the system?!
システムに入れない人はどうするの！
それは違うって　どうやって言えばいいのよ！
How are we supposed
to tell people that it's wrong?!
この
You!
高いとこから偉そうに言うな！
Don't you dare look down
on others, you egotistical punk!
組織に入るしかない人はどうなる！
What about those who have
no choice but join the system?!
正義とは！！
What is justice?!
藤堂さんと千葉
侵略者のやりかたに従えば
When you follow an aggressor's
methods, you legitimize them!
その行為を認めたことになる
でも　ここで出撃されたら死んでしまいます！
But if you go into
battle now, you'll die!
You!
And you call yourself a!
おおまえはそれでも！
はっとする千葉
すまない
I'm sorry.
え
私はこういう生き方しか
This is the only way
I know how to live.
倒れる藤堂さん
藤堂さん！
Tohdoh!
天子
どうして争いなんて
Why do people
have to fight?!
守るべきものが　あるのなら！
Because I have something
I must protect!
血をはきながら戦うシンクー
戦のあり方に
Perhaps war has been robbed
of its dignity and morality.
矜持と美学が失われているのやもしれんな
それでも　居場所は必要だったから
Even so,
I needed a place to belong.
と同じ部屋にいるヴィレッタ
ただそれだけで戦ってきたのに
For only that reason,
we've fought.
なあ直人　俺達これでよかったのかな？
Oh, Naoto... Was this all
really for the best for us?
でも戦争は発明の母っていうよねえ
Still, they say that war
is the mother of invention.
認めないよ
I don't accept that. You don't see the people
who come before that, Earl of Pudding.
プリン伯爵はその先にある人間をみていないからさ
二ーナとかいったっけ
Nina, was it?
What about you?
あんたはどうなんだい？
わ私はただ　やれることを
l- I was just doing
what I could...
繰り返したくなかっただけなんです
We just didn't want
it to happen again.
ふうんでも人は弱いからさ
But people are weak.
そうだよ！夢くらいみてぇじゃねか！
救護室で手当てをうける玉城
That's right!
Even I have dreams, don't I?!
なのに俺にはその資格もねえってのか？
But now they say I don't
have any right to them?!
まだやれるのにやれるのによぉ
Even though I can still fight!
Even though I can!
なんでみんな俺をバカにするんだよぉ！
Why does everyone
treat me like a fool?!
先輩
Tamaki-san...
私は見てきた
I've seen it.
I've seen it over and over.
見続けてきた
抗うことが人の歴史だと
Human history is
one of opposition. Even so!
しかし
人は　世界は　こんなにも思い通りにならない！
People... The world... Despite it all,
they won't be what we want them to be!
だから　思い通りにしようって言うの？！
And so now you're
forcing them to be?!
それは
That's!
ナナリーとルルーシュ
それは卑劣なのです
That's despicable!
人の心をねじまげ
Using Geass, which bends people's
minds and tramples on their dignity!
尊厳をふみにじるギアスは
ではダモクレスはどうだ？
Then what about Damocles?
強制的に人を従わせる
Isn't it a system to force people
to obey just as despicable?!
卑劣なシステムではないのか？
ダモクレスは　憎しみの象徴になります
Damocles will become
the symbol of their hatred.
憎しみはここに集めるんです
Their hatred will be focused here.
So that everyone will move towards the future.
みんなで明日を迎えるためにも
そうかナナリー　おまえも
I see. Nunnally, you got
the same idea. In that case...
なら
ルルーシュ·ヴィ·ブリタニアが命じる
Lelouch vi Britannia commands you!
ダモクレスの鍵を渡せ！
Give me the Damocles key!
ギアスをつかうルルーシュ
いや
No! I mustn't give it to you!
お兄様に　渡してはいけない！
これ以上罪を！
All the sins you've committed!
だけど負けました
どうぞ　お兄様
Here you go, big brother.
ダモクレスの鍵を渡します
うっ！うこしゃくな
Impudent!
記録終了
Recording, complete.
まだまだ～！
NOT QUITE!
はっ！
爆散！！
Detonate!
くっううっ
記憶せよ！
Memorize this!
Make a record of Jeremiah Gottwald!
ジェレミア·ゴットバルト！
機体からとびだして宙を舞うジェレミアが素敵過ぎる
おまえに敗北をもたらした
Commemorate the name of
the man who defeated you!
記念すべき男の名前だ
記念？関係ない
Commemorate? That has nothing
to do with it. I have no memories...
どうせ私には記憶が
記憶？まさか
No memories? Could it be?!
機体と格闘するジノ
動け　トリスタン！せめて飛ぶことだけでも
C'mon, Tristan, move!
Just let me fly!
カレンとスザク
くっこれで輻射波動も弾切れ
Even the radiant wave surger
is out of ammo now.
シールドエナジーも尽きたかとスザク
My shield energy's
exhausted now, too?
それでも！
Even so!
決めきれない
I can't beat her! Even using
the curse that Geass has given me!
ギアスの呪いをつかっているのに
カレン　なんて強さだ
Kallen, your strength
is unimaginable!
スペックはこっちが上のはずなのに
My machine has better specs
than yours, and yet...
スザク　これだけの力があって！なんで！
Suzaku, with your strength...
WHY?!
終わりにしよう　カレン！
Let's end it, Kallen!
あなたに！正義さえあれば！
If you just had justice
on your side!
ぐぅ
そんな届かなかったの？
No... It didn't get him?!
いや　届いているよ　カレン
No, Kallen... You got me.
紅蓮の腕がささっていました
そうか　勝ったのかカレン
I see... You won, Kallen...
ナナリー
Nunnally...
おまえはもう立派に自分の考えで生きている
You now live following your own
thoughts without help from others.
だからこそ　俺も
Which means I am now free
to follow the path I must.
俺の道をすすむことができる
鍵をうけとるルルーシュ
ありがとう
Thank you.
愛してる　ナナリー
I love you, Nunnally.
はっと元にもどるナナリー
あっつかったのですね　ギアスを
You used your Geass
on me, didn't you?!
ルルーシュは背を向けて歩いて行きました
待ちなさい！
Wait!
あっ
待ちなさい　待って！　あっ
Wait! Stop!
車いすから階段におちてしまうナナリー
お兄様は悪魔です！
You're a monster!
卑劣で　卑怯で　なんてなんてひどい
Despicable! Cowardly!
How can you?
How can you be so cruel?!
うっ
ナナリーをそのままに いってしまうルルーシュ
裏切りの騎士　枢木スザクが敗れたそうです
The traitorous knight Suzaku
Kururugi has apparently been killed.
命乞いをしてはいただけませんの？
Aren't you going to beg for your life?
For his sake, at least?
あの方のために
神楽耶
Kaguya... You never knew
Lelouch's true face until recently.
おまえは最近までルルーシュの素顔を知らなかった
それが何か？
What of it?
なのに　本質の一部を理解していた
Even so, you understood
a bit of his true nature.
おまえは　やさしいな
You're a kind girl.
全世界に告げる
Attention, World!
私は　神聖ブリタニア帝国皇帝
I am Lelouch vi Britannia,
emperor of the Holy Britannian Empire!
ルルーシュ·ヴィ·ブリタニアである
バカな！ルルーシュがフレイヤをつかったということは！
Impossible! If Lelouch used
the F.L.E.I.J.A., then that means!
そんな！
No!
嘘だろ！
No way!
シュナイゼルも我が軍門にくだった
Schneizel has
surrendered to me.
これによってダモクレスもフレイヤもすべて私のものとなった
Because of this, I now control both
Damocles and the F.L.E.I.J.A.s.
黒の騎士団も　私に抵抗する力は残っていない
And even the Black Knights no longer
have the strength to oppose me.
それでも抗うというのなら
If anyone dare oppose me now,
they shall know the power of F.L.E.I.J.A.!
フレイヤの力を知ることになるだけだ
我が覇道を阻むものはもはや存在しない
Those who can challenge
my military rule no longer exist!
そう　今日この日　この瞬間をもって
Yes! From this day, from this moment
forward, the world belongs to me!
世界は我が手に落ちた
ルルーシュ·ヴィ·ブリタニアが命じる
Lelouch vi Britannia commands you!
世界よ　我に従え！
Obey me, World!
オール　ハイル　ルルーシュ！
All hail Lelouch!
All hail Lelouch! All hail Lelouch!
オール　ハイル　ルルーシュ！
2 MONTHS LATER...
Imperial Crown Colony of Japan
神聖ブリタニア帝国　第99代　唯一皇帝陛下にして
And now, the 99th and sole emperor
of the Holy Britannian Empire,
黒の騎士団CEO
as well as CEO of the Black Knights and the
current chairman of the U.F.N. Supreme Council,
超合集国　第二代最高評議会議長であらせられる
ルルーシュ·ヴィ·ブリタニア様のお姿がみえました
His Majesty Lelouch vi Britannia
has come into view.
そしてご覧ください
And look at this, too.
愚かにも　ルルーシュ様に反逆したものたちが
Those who foolishly opposed Emperor Lelouch
are being taken to the execution grounds.
処刑場へと運ばれて行きます
先の大戦で　帝都ペンドラゴンや多くの将兵
While it was paid for with the sacrifices of
the capital, Pendragon, the lives of many soldiers,
そしてナイトオブゼロ
as well as the life of Sir Suzaku Kururugi,
the Knight of Zero, in the recent great war,
枢木スザク卿という尊い犠牲を払いつつも
ＥＵが超合集国憲章を批准した今
now that the E.U. has ratified the
United Federation of Nations charter,
我らがルルーシュ様が　ついに世界統一という偉業をなしとげられたのです
Emperor Lelouch has finally achieved
the grand task of unifying the world!
ルルーシュ様に栄光あれ
Glory to His Majesty Lelouch!
オール　ハイル　ブリタニア
All hail Britannia! All hail Lelouch!
オール　ハイル　ルルーシュ
何が栄光だ
スザクの墓石や ひかれていく反逆者の中には
Glory, my ass.
ただの独裁だろ
This is just a dictatorship.
逆らうものはすべて殺して
Anyone who disobeys him is killed!
し！誰かにきかれたら　一族皆殺しにされるわ
Shh! If somebody hears you,
they'll kill your entire family!
こんなものを正義として報道しなきゃならんとは
報道陣
I can't believe we have to
broadcast this and call it justice!
ルルーシュ
Lelouch, is that what
you wanted to do?
これがおまえがやりたかったことなのかよ
世界をみんなを支配して
To control the world?
To control everyone?!
ラクシャータ 咲世子 セシル　ニーナ
バカだねえ～あんたたちは
You all weren't very bright.
あそこでルルーシュにさからってさえいなきゃさ
If you hadn't disobeyed
Lelouch when you did...
明日を迎えるためです
It was so we could
move into the future.
成功と失敗をくりかえして前にすすむ
Through repeated success
and failure, we advance.
科学と同じじゃないでしょうか 人も
That goes for people
as well as for science.
それが進化
That's evolution.
進歩でしょプリン伯爵
You mean progress,
don't you, Earl of Pudding?
その呼び方
That name you call me...
まだ恨んでんの？
Are you still bitter about that?
さあ　どっちでしょう
Maybe. I'm not sure.
ロイド先生とラクシャータさんって
Dr. Lloyd and Ms. Rakshata...
ん？
昔何かあったんですか？
Did something happen
between them before?
ささいなことよ
It's hardly worth mentioning.
あとから考えてみたらなんてことはない
When I think about it now,
it wasn't really anything.
出発点てだけ
It was just a starting point.
再びパレード
あっ！扇！
扇の姿をみかけていこうとするヴィレッタをとめるコーネリア
Ohgi!
今でていけばおもうつぼだ
If you go out now, you'll be
playing right into their hands!
しかし
But!
そのときどよめきが
なんだ？
What is that?
ゼロが行く手に立っていました
ゼロ！？
あっ　ゼロ！？
Zero?!
ゼ ゼロって
Zero!
Z-Zero?!
うそ？！
It can't be!
Lelouch is over there!
ルルーシュはあそこに！
とカレン
教会で祈りをささげるC.C.
まさか
ルルーシュたちがやろうとしたことって
Is that it?! Is that what Lelouch
and the others were doing?!
とカレン
ナイトメアの銃弾を神業な動きかわし
撃つな！私が相手をする！
Cease fire!
I'll take care of him!
しかしジェレミアの頭を踏み台にしていくゼロ
行け　仮面の騎士よ
Onward, masked knight.
ゼロはルルーシュのもとへ
痴れ者が！
Fool!
ルルーシュの銃をはじきとばし剣をつきつけるゼロ
スザク　約束どおり　おまえが俺を殺せ
Suzaku... You have to kill me,
like you promised.
やるのか？どうしても
You're going through with this?
No matter what?
予定通り　世界の憎しみは今この俺に集まっている
As planned, the world's hatred
is focused on me.
あとは俺が消えることで
All that remains is to get rid of
me and break the chain of hatred.
この憎しみの連鎖を断ち切るだけだ
黒の騎士団にはゼロという伝説が残っている
ゼロの仮面をさしだすルルーシュ
The legend of Zero lives on
in the Black Knights.
シュナイゼルもゼロにつかえる
Schneizel will serve Zero, too.
これで世界は軍事力ではなく
With this, the world will be able to
gather not through force of arms,
話しあいというひとつのテーブルにつくことができる
but around one table for discussion.
明日をむかえることができる
They can move forward
into the future.
ゼロの仮面をうけとるスザク
それが
And that...
ああ
Yes.
ゼロ　レクイエム
is the Zero Requiem.
ルルーシュを刺すゼロ（スザク）
Ｃの世界で僕らは知った
We both knew it back in Cs' World.
人々が明日を望んでいることを
How people were
longing for the future.
なあ　スザク
Say, Suzaku...
Geass is like a wish, isn't it?
願いとは　ギアスに似ていないか
えっ？
自分の力だけではかなわないことを
It's a request to someone to give you the
power to achieve what you can't on your own.
誰かに求める
願いか
A wish, huh?
そう俺は人々を願いという名のギアスにかける
Yes. I'm going to cast the
Geass called a wish on people.
世界の明日のために
For the future of the world.
祈るC.C.
ルルーシュおまえは
Lelouch... The price of the Geass
you're going to cast on them is!
人々にギアスをかけた代償として
撃っていいのは　撃たれる覚悟のあるやつだけだ
The only people who should kill are
those prepared to die themselves!
スザク　おまえは英雄になるんだ
Suzaku...
You're going to be a hero now.
世界の敵　皇帝ルルーシュ·ヴィ·ブリタニアから世界を救った救世主
As the messiah who saved the world...
from Emperor Lelouch vi Britannia,
the enemy of the world.
ゼロに
As Zero.
ゼロ（スザク）の剣がルルーシュの胸をつらぬきます
ルルルーシュ
L... Lelouch!
仮面の下で涙を流すスザク
これは　おまえにとっても罰だ
This, then,
shall be your punishment.
おまえは正義の味方として
You will live on, wearing that mask,
as the knight of justice.
仮面をかぶり続ける
枢木スザクとして生きることはもう　ない
You will no longer live
as Suzaku Kururugi.
人並みの幸せも　すべて世界にささげてもらう
You shall sacrifice your own ordinary
pleasure to the world... forevermore...
永遠に
そのギアス　確かにうけとった
This Geass... I do accept.
倒れるルルーシュはそのままころげおちて
お兄様？
Big brother?
ルルーシュの手をとったナナリーにはすべて伝わりました
そんなお兄様は　今まで
No... Everything you did
until now was!
うっお兄様　愛しています！
Big brother, I love you!
あぁ俺は
Yes... I...
世界を壊し
I destroy... the world...
世界を
and create it...
つくる
anew...
ルルーシュ死亡
お兄様！いや！
Big brother! No!
Please, open your eyes!
目をあけてください！
お兄様～！お兄様～～！
Big brother! BIG BROTHER!!!
ルルーシュにとりすがって泣くナナリー
魔王ルルーシュは死んだぞ！
The demon Lelouch is dead!
Free the prisoners!
人質を解放しろ！
というコーネリアの掛け声
Right!
ヴィレッタに続く兵士と人々
いかん　ひけ！この場はひくんだ！
Uh-oh. Retreat!
Retreat, at once!
まさか　あれは
Is it possible? Is that?
ゼロです
It's Zero!
あれは　ゼロです！
That's... That's Zero there!
ずるいです
It's not fair... All I needed to
be happy was to be with you!
私はお兄様だけでよかったのに
お兄様のいない明日なんて
How can I face
the future without you?
そんなの
ゼロ　ゼロ　ゼロ　ゼロ　ゼロ　ゼロ...
Zero! Zero! Zero! Zero!
ねえルルーシュ
Well, Lelouch, the world's gotten
a lot better since that day.
あれから世界はずいぶんましになったわ
戦争にむいていたエネルギーは
All the energy once
directed towards war...
今　飢餓や貧困にふりむけられている
has now been turned toward
solving hunger and poverty.
いろんな憎しみや悪事は
All sorts of hatreds and evil
deeds have been laid at your feet.
ほとんどあなた一人に押しつけられて
みんな　ダモクレスというシステムより
Maybe that's because
the name of a person...
名前のあるひとりのほうがわかりやすかったってことかしら
is easier for people to blame
than a system called Damocles.
調子のいい話よね
We're so quick to
simplify our past troubles.
でも だからこそ
But still,
perhaps because of that,
みんなは過去にとらわれず
people are free of the past and able
to move forward into the future now.
先にすすめるのかもしれない
計算どおりだって　あなたは笑うのかしら
I wonder if you're laughing now about how
it all went according to your calculations.
もちろん　いろんな問題は残ってるけど
Of course, all sorts of problems
remain. But, even so...
それでも
ギアスという名の王の力が人を孤独にする
Geass, the power of the king,
isolates people.
ふうん　少しだけ違っていたか
Maybe that's not quite correct.
なぁ　ルルーシュ
Right, Lelouch?
至此本字幕已全部更新完毕
Dakuse wa oni
This corrupt world is filled with demons
Seigi wa nanzo to
What is justice?
感谢一直支持诸神字幕组的亲们
Tou mae ni aragae yo
Resist, don't just question
Akutoku no hana
The flower of evil
正因为有各位的支持 我们才有动力继续为各位制作更多双语作品
Gizen no yume
Dreams of hypocrisy
Mishi me niwa me wo sashi
Give your gaze to the eyes that see them
若有什么意见或建议欢迎访问www.kamigami.org联系我们
Sei mo ja mo wakatareru koto nashi
The line between right and wrong cannot be known
或是发现有字幕中错误之处请联系QQ8ww27868421
Hikari wa tae taiji no you ni
Light is gone, and you slumber
Kimi wa nemuru yami no shikyuu
Like an unborn child in the womb of darkness
Kodoku koso itooshii
Isolation is what you love
Yui-itsu no mikata to naru darou
It will probably be your only ally
Hitori hitori chishio ni mamire
One by one, stained with the tide of blood
Kono jidai ni umare ochita
You were born into this era
Erabareshi oujira yo
Oh, chosen princes
Tatakai koso shukuen
Battle shall be your banquet
Aa ware wa uruwashii zenchi
Oh, I am graceful omniscience
Ai no haha
The loving mother
Kimi wo umu
Who bore you
Kono chichi ni hagukumishi mono wa
The ones who were raised on my breast
Jigoku no harakara
Are your brethren in hell
Mokushi no in
The mark of apocalypse
Shinri wa nanzo to
What is truth
Shirimosezu uzumoreshi intoku no tane
A seed of secrecy buried where no one knows
Moroha no ken
A double-edged sword
Nuku ha niwa ha wo muke
Turn its blade upon the unsheathed blade
Mamorubeki mono dake wo shinjite
Believe only in what you must protect
Aru ga mama ni kimi wa
And in your own way
Kimi wo hanate
You'll set yourself free